Hey, we're back. Sorry about that
Hi, I just have to go I guess go delete that last stream real quick. So I don't
Come across any issues, but we're having some fun and we're not gonna let a little a
Little form on getting our way of having some fun. Okay good. Okay, so let's get that stream
I can actually delete it. And then I'll be good. Okay.
Yo, thank you.
What's up? Another day at the office, a big black dick.
I was like, Oh,
The ghost is being friendly again. Oh my gosh. Yeah, I was surprised that's a ghost because in Elise's chat that guy was like an asshole.
Oh yeah, I think it's a different ghost. Let me see. Ghost? Is that the real ghost? I don't know.
Yeah, that's me.
Okay, good.
I have a question. Can I ask a question?
Is that okay?
Thank you, why don't you and Chris get into that fight that uh that one time we got into a fight
Yeah, you guys when you remember it was all funny. You guys be talking, you know behind the scenes
What was that I don't know what you're talking about we had a fight
Yeah, well it was a funny fight, it was a mock fight, it was an actual fight.
I know more than one Chris.
Who's Chris?
Do you know JD Crucible? Cause I don't know if it's a right, you got the right JD with you, right?
Oh, I do, yeah, and how it started at the end, it was like, yeah, I was just wondering why you guys wanted to happen.
It wasn't like a real fight or nothing, it was a funny fight.
Okay, well J. Did you know how it turns Chris? Okay. Hold on. Let me recollect my memory. Let me let me do my marble jangler
It was that no, well, don't meet you. So it was a I think it's like the staff
What's the one about the restaurant the restaurant one yeah, why do you guys play explain that to me real quick if you don't mind I
Mean don't you know?
Nope, I'm asking you
Well, it was an argument about a restaurant
Are you sure it wasn't because he has an impersonation that he does of you you sure that's not the real reason
It was about the restaurant. It was about the food. No one ever did an impersonation of me ever
No one ever does any book impersonations of me. I
Remember how are you doing?
Yeah, he was very insulting
I just looked that up and that was you brother. If it's really you that was you
My stomach all right, I only have a little bit of lead in my system. I'm not gonna remember everything
This isn't such an even convention. Why are we interrogating me? Yeah, I know
No, I'm calling bullshit on you. I'm calling bullshit. I'm saying you're not who you are
And also that was easy question. I just fucking
Shut the fuck up
Who do I say you're not the real ghost
One of many one of many, you know, I got about 30 different accounts here, uh, but these are to make shit up
Yeah, we have people that don't believe that you're the real JD. I think the real JD
Oh, it's an origin story time. Yeah, go ahead. Tell your how much
How much money do you pay to have this dude up here then you only got like you only had two people watching when he joined so
That's what he's talking about leave me alone
Oh, go so you're about to get you. Come on. Let's, uh, so what's Amy Cavill's profile picture. Let me see
But no, so JT tell me about tan mom though
Do you have any tan mom stories or experiences of working with tan mom? Like she just seems like an interesting lady
She's uh, a stinky old bag who smells like booze barely could stand
She's reasonable half the time though
We're there when she does a Nicole Kidman cancer thing
Do you know what though those they had they had like one of the the staff like
didn't like he was like 12 years old and make a wish foundation and then
They told they said oh we told him you're Nicole Kidman and she came out doing a like an Australian accident
I think I remember that that's so long ago. I remember more of like the octa mom situation
Do you remember the octa mom? Yeah, yeah, yeah, that lady on a bunch of times. Um, that bitch was crazy
Who has like 10 kids?
Oh, well, you know more Mormon people Mormons are yeah, I mean at once. Yeah, it was just crazy
That's like an octopus like it really is like an octopus. Yeah, literally like octopus. Yeah, he was insane
well imagine her vagina must been stretched out like a
Sure after that delivery, I mean it's like wow
Like go sass hole
Well, yeah, she had a litter of kids.
How about, did you ever see Martina King?
Did you ever see that lady?
She's a, this is a German lady that turned black.
Oh, the one who tanned herself?
Yeah, she had these injections,
like in return of her and her husband, both black,
but she's like, she has these huge boobs, like huge.
Like,
But like the ones that kind of crushed the watermelons like that kind of side like there's just this enormously
comic breast implants that it's like nobody would have to crush the beer cans not the watermelons
Yeah, but she's pretty classic
Do you have any, like, favorite guests or, like, any guests that was, like, um, different on camera than off or, like, I don't know, how about Jeff the Drunk?
Do you have any good stories?
Let's see.
I think if I had to think about it, what's his name?
Fucking Eric.
Eric's favorite.
Eric's midget.
Yeah.
High-pitched Eric.
Oh, high-pitched Eric.
Okay.
Oh, speaking of which, he's going to be on the LCU very soon.
We hooked him up.
Oh, the laughing cow or something show?
Yeah, the little cow show Keemstar is interested in high-pitched Eric.
Okay.
You might be actually making some severe money soon.
Well, I...
Heard high-pitched Eric call in to Elisa's and he didn't have a high-pitched voice. He was he talked like oh, no
No, he sounds like a normal kind of person sometimes
Really deep boy, I was like oh my
Yeah, it's almost like he put on the act for 20 years or something
Yeah, I mean that's crazy. That's dedication to his role. My favorite episode I think was when
like he came in for his birthday once and they put him in like a rainbow wig and like I don't
think they put a fish around him. We revolved around the harassing him with fish.
I don't remember the fish. What fish? He was afraid of fish and so they when he brought him this
like dead fish he would scream like get away from me get away. Oh Eric's fucking
I thought he was afraid of parents.
So people aren't thinking you're not JD.
Yes, you are JD.
This is, it's verifiable.
I am the JD from the Howard Stone Show,
from the Elisa Jordana Show.
When she answered the phone when I first called in,
she said, oh JD, I'm JD.
Well, this is, she knows,
she knows that I'm JD, right?
So were you there when she was around the time she was developed must have been in 2012 or 2010 it was just 2009
2009 I think wow
Can you believe how time flies was like 15 years ago or something like that and
Yeah, I mean, it's like I find her like like like with Benji and like her like some of her exes like you know
Andy Dick and stuff like that is that I don't know Benji's bisexual or something like that
But he has like you know, you know, he's odd, right?
He's just an unusual but um like I just don't see her like being like that sexual with people
But it's like or she needs that like
Yeah
people, it's of the younger variety. We'll just put it that way.
I mean, I'm not trying to say anything, but do you see her when the teenage boys in Florida come up to her and she's like, but anyone else, anyone with money, any normal age person?
Well, it is like, you know, that area is like a retiree place. And so every place she goes, she's like the youngest one in the room usually. So it's probably nice to meet some younger people.
and her pride, no one was like,
and then like Star, Cobra, Cobra Starship or whatever.
Oh, Cobra, whatever, yeah, yeah.
She got kicked out of the band.
Yeah, in trouble for the teenagers on the bus.
The teenagers in the bus and sort of in alcohol
and they like stole the iPads of the band
or something like that.
Yeah, that's against a lot of laws.
J.D. doesn't have a New York accent. What the fuck are you talking about?
He's putting on a New York accent today more than he usually has.
I'm putting it on. I'm putting it on. I'm putting it on. Obviously. Come on. I'm a star.
It's cool. My first time new channel.
Casey says you were a caller. You said sounds like J.D. We used to trick and engage.
We used to trick and engage chat. Is that true, J.D.?
What do you mean trick?
I don't know, have I been hoodwinked?
Like people gotta tell me more, what do you mean?
I don't know, well KZ is just a nut, he's like,
he thinks that like, oh, that'd be like,
I mean, how obscure of a troll is it to like,
have a fake JD and like just for months have me have a,
I mean, that'd be just-
Well, I don't know, it's almost like
if you're desperate and you're on a live stream,
there's somebody calls in,
and you randomly call them JD.
Randomly, well.
Yeah.
You want to become GD, huh, Maya?
Well, it's fine.
So even if you're not, who are you?
Yoners or something like that?
You're somebody.
Hold on.
You know who Yoners is?
No, I don't know who that is.
You don't know who that is?
All I know is that I'm a highly valued comedian.
No!
Okay, well, you know guys even if he's not JD. I mean he actually has a better personality than jade. I thought JD would have
So you probably should pull it off as a bit. I should call him JD. Just saying
I am the real JD
Yeah, I guess you might be the real JD, you're not that JD though.
You could be like, oh, let's pretend like, you know, you have Johnny Def from the moment.
I don't like Brad Pitt, and it's like, I think it's Brad Pitt.
No one's calling for it. Just look up his voice, it doesn't sound the same at all.
I've already done vocal figure printing, it is, I have a...
You didn't do, you did none of that, you did none of that.
Do not lie to me, so...
Do not lie.
I am definitely the real JD, hard maya here.
And if I'm not soon, and I am the real goes
Yeah, I just I actually looked up the real
Well, not you sir, but I actually looked up JD and you saw nothing like it nice and close in comparison
That's why I actually that simple party question you couldn't answer. No one's falling for the bet
I mean if you said it was a bit would have been funny every one with it, but since you've made it serious
Are you in charge do you feel in charge?
I'm definitely in charge of this this whole community. Do you feel in charge?
Would you like to see that tree?
The cult of psyche is my own this is now the cult of JD
No longer the cult of psyche
Golden apples pearl
Yeah, oh my gosh. She's spreading chaos in my chat guys. What am I gonna do?
Damn right. I don't know how to do with chaos, you know
Actually, the show is like basically just chaotic. I mean, I mean, that's a good point. The show is kind of chaos
What is the G stand for by the way?
just dick. Just dick. Oh good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job.
me using a fake New York accent. It's him, guys. It's him.
Is this night police? Or is this night police?
It's like, look up. Just let me know. Just leave real quick and look up one of his videos.
It doesn't sound like him at all. Hey, I've watched so much hours there.
Bloody hell.
Okay, I mean it's like it's really matter. Just pretend it's JD even if it's not I fucking him
I'm gonna fight. You know what if this is the world if this is actually him I'll get $500 right now
All right, if it's not if it's not him you're gonna give me $250 so you want to bet
Okay, yeah, I just won that fucking debate dumb dumps
I I know I know people from the lease of Jordana
You're welcome, but you got kicked out again, right?
Yeah, because I doubled down and called her a dumb cunt.
I don't know what I did.
Well, I mean, gosh, I got three people back into that discord
and like all three of them have just went,
hey, here's a J-dog once they had you.
I'm going to be a J-dog on the show.
Let's welcome J-dog.
J-dog.
Is this the real J-dog?
Yeah.
That's the real J-dog.
Okay.
Psyche, what's up?
What's up a dog? How are you? What's good pampin challenge?
This is JD from Howard Stern show and we have
Oh, what's going on JD from Howard's?
What's going on?
$10 KZ
I don't know whether to play along with the bit or I'm having a difficult time here.
My god, ghost, ghost.
You need to take the medication, you need to take the poison.
Obviously, we play along.
Oh, okay, never mind.
You know what? You remind me that you have to take my pill. My bad.
Jesus Christ.
Remember, always take an anti-psychotic before going on a live stream.
Yeah, JD, you don't have to go psych out.
I'm the real ghost. There's not only one ghost here, Jerry.
You won't forget what I sound like if you take an anti-psychotic.
Ghost will roll over you.
Can I be honest with you, sir?
You kind of sound like a dumb dog.
Honestly, I'm not trying to be rude.
I sound like a dum-dum.
You kind of sound like a... you kind of... can I be honest?
Do I sound like a dum-dum?
Do you lie up and miss him too, Chris?
There he goes
Why is the KZ's in the cat bitching why is KZ keep bitching if he hasn't paid psyche yet?
I don't know
Jay dog up and not me
Yeah
He needs to pay the fine KZ has refused to pay the fine. He knows the rules already, but he refuses to follow me about this
Well KZ well psyche psyche psyche's rule because you know
It's like, can you explain it to him because you could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could have played better than I could
Okay
Right there goes your like
Well, we let you back up
I'm not a dumbass
Doesn't get what you might be a dumb dumb. I didn't say don't
Either no no J-Dog is definitely not a dumb dumb ghost
You know that you might be you might be a I know it
I know ghosts has some type of autism, I don't know what type but I'm on the spectrum
There's nothing wrong with being on the spectrum, but it's just you know
Well, everybody's on a spectrum, because the spectrum is like, it takes everybody, right?
Yeah, it's different levels. It's different levels. It's just there, you get everybody has it.
Yeah, there's levels in this dumb dumb shit here.
Yup, yup, some of us are lower, some of us are higher.
I'll sit on the levels to the dumb dumb shit.
I can't hear you so I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I can't hear you, I
Like like I said, she has that like you know this energy just like very
Well, we're talking about my sex life
Yeah, why are you gay first?
Hold on hold on I'm gonna send you a DM on this
Okay, hold on. Okay, never mind. It's not gonna be
Y'all be back
I couldn't hear shit because of fucking what's his face? Yeah. Oh, yeah
Jay dog. It was the win
If you fucking come
Ghost you're more annoying with your voice and you are with the type
I didn't think it was fucking possible how how you could be more annoying, but you are
Well, then I got a point here then I just like heard you wrong
Fucking you should have let me on the bed site. You should I'm sorry
Why would you not let me on the bed? Why would you not tell me that?
What would you not say that half the people in the world? I don't fucking know. I'm retarded
You should have let me on the bit though. I would lucky Pierre. No one is at the bed. Oh, you gotta use fucking text me site
Hey, are you gonna use fucking text me? Hey?
It's fucking that easy dude
Did I not talk to you like 15 minutes ago?
He wasn't
Oh Jesus Christ, he said something
I ruined the bed and I feel like a piece of shit
I ruined it, I know
God damn it
Oh
He needs to know everything psyche you need to tell him when you shit you need to tell him when you piss he can't just
Control himself. He couldn't be nice. I guess I guess I have no impulse control my bad
I already can see that you're not beating me up brother. I said sorry
You need to be ready go at it J-Doc. Oh fuck. Yeah, I spoke way more than this
You fucking assholes, why did you tell my mom that's the thought we were doing something today?
See my kitty cat?
Yes, it's a cute little black cat.
McAree Beans. Goddamn, I know I need to leave. I thought shit.
You don't.
Oh god. Oh my god. Her name is Lenore. She's like the little mascot. She's the cult mascot.
Oh, so cute.
You know, she actually talks, she recorded a promo for my show. It's just a few seconds,
but yeah, this is Lenore filming this herself. She's a really amazing cinematographer.
Garden of broken gods we plant our screens like seeds out of pixels prayer grows
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion between the wound and the one who tends it
We are gathered in the glow of screens our rosaries made of emojis our hymns corrupted files
Yet still we rise singing through distortion the cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth
There you go
I love the cult of psyche. I love that cat. Oh, thank you. This is a wonderful show
You have wonderful people on here. Look at these people in the chat. Let's see
KZ still going off like a freak
Big time is over there with his wrench talking J-Dog recently proved. He's not gay by going to a gay bar on stream by himself and dancing. Yes, I
Did that
Yeah, he would do a gay bar and dance, but you know what, straight guy, that is confidence,
right?
Do we want to do another one?
I don't know how many gay bars.
He's gotten more gay bars than I've been to, but you know, I haven't been to very many
though.
He doesn't look like he goes to gay bars, it's interesting.
He's very secure in his sexuality.
He looks like a daddy.
He does look like a daddy.
He actually, he mooned somebody on stream recently.
So are you familiar with the name Bita?
I don't even know who Bita is.
I guess you haven't.
I don't know anything.
If you watched him, like,
that's not clip I was playing before
and it was that woman with a really high pitched voice.
Cause actually, I was stream rated by Shuli,
like right when I had like,
probably after I monetized in the other channel,
he rated me one day on stream, just like coincidentally,
right?
And
And that was like, that was pretty cool.
So also I've had Wendy on the show
and also, I don't know if you know Minnie Manson, but...
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Manson, I know him.
Minnie Manson has been on the show, a friend of the show.
I can't believe he actually streamed to police
and like, people didn't like him.
I thought he was great, I thought he did a good job.
Well, the first time I saw him on like I watched like these clips because I only started watching at least like probably like like July of last year
but I saw these clips and the first like she was interviewing him over like the
Honor permanent friend show and he is like she got she called calling him mini Mason and then he kept getting so mad and then he was like
I'm gonna slice your throat bitch
I was like, oh my god. I was like, I can't believe that I'd be scary and then like
i was like i'm sure she never saw him again and then like a year later they were streaming together like
and they're driving around like to griffith park and the mini manson's like having a panic attack
in the car because that's not a medication i looked at and they dropped me off bitch this is so
that man that man is one of the kind mini manson deserves like a lot more support than he gets
Yeah, Minnie Manson is a true, I think a national treasure.
I like him more than Marilyn Manson, actually this one.
But yeah, Minnie Manson did flip out one time
and then one of my discord posted a lot of weird shit.
I've never seen such weird shit.
Very cool artistic stuff though, like, I don't know.
Did the way he stares into the camera?
Very intense.
He's performed more at blues.
On the show a few times, he's, I don't know if you're going to go like,
Oh, Brad, Billy, have you heard of Billy?
Who's Billy, right, the song?
Billy, the fridge?
Yeah, Billy, that does the racist songs, like he's like,
the house next door has been sold to Enwords or something like that.
I don't know if that's the same guy.
I don't know if that's the same Billy either.
I don't want to label him as a racist.
Yeah, but at least the ministry was classic.
Yeah, I mean she's actually said I could go stream with her if I could get down to Florida like I'm really yeah
You're gonna do that. I would love to I mean it's and I might actually have somebody that wants to help
sponsor that too, and so it might happen
But yeah, I got along with her since I started calling the show
Like and it's like I've never had a problem with her but people there's so many people like oh my god
She's so evil and like yeah, yeah people don't have a problem with her until they have a problem
That's the thing the guy on Jimmy the Christian or whatever like you know that story. Yeah, that's that yeah
Yeah, I'm a manifesto right that guy manifesto guy and stuff and then it's like well because she like I don't she didn't like
Like she all she all I heard her say about it was like, oh, I think he's like, you know
He was born like sick and he can help what he was doing and he gets sickness like that
And then that's all but she didn't like condemn him like really he's in prison for 500 years. Yeah, I think I've five hundred years
Yeah, so that's like he'll I mean he'll be very very old when he gets out
Yeah, but people would say that oh just because like I like her they'd be like
Trying to associate me with him and I was watching her show and he was around and plus
I don't care if she condemns somebody or not. It's like
He's already being punished enough. I guess but whatever happens that one retarded lady. Oh, oh my god, there's too many of them
Okay, well, she's the one that I thought she was like Albert Einstein. Yeah, yeah Albert Einstein from yeah
She calls in the middle of the night she's like
Installing me and they're like they're like police officer
People who live in the fucking house are the fucking people who work in the hotels and shit. They're like what the fuck?
We can't get her up and they have that like 5150 her that was crazy
She's gonna kick that everywhere. I feel really bad for her
All right, yokey on my don't die don't die
Yeah, I love that episode when then Elise like finds her on the bridge
She does the edges on the bridge, yeah
And she's on a bridge with all these cops around her, and she's like, that's my friend, that's my friend, but at least it was like, what?
And then actually like she like
I told like K jobs like went out there like thinking like you know
She's gonna be like staying at Lisa's house or whatever and at least it like referred her to like the local hostel
Yeah, so I don't think at least
Should be tell I always said Lisa is more security, you know, it's like because she at least needed
I always told her at least one security guy
She doesn't listen because she doesn't want to spend the money. Yeah, it's good. Wow
She has I've seen her chased down the street by a lady with like five knives in her purse. I've seen her
Yeah, this one lady had five knives in her purse and then she like through Lisa's
Person the street and then Alisa started running screaming
knocking on police car windows saying this woman's crazy. She's after me
She has five knives in her purse and then I saw her when she was
She met this guy, Jadus, the person that he's talking about.
Oh, Jadus, yes.
Yeah, do you know Jadus?
I know him.
And she was like, before he went in with him,
she like went and searched his car for like weapons.
Oh, yeah, yeah, they handcuffed him, didn't they?
Yeah, Jadus, oh, he handcuffed?
Yeah, she like, said she'd meet him, but she hadn't handcuffed him.
But the funniest handcuffs I saw was when she had L.A. Sparta, like Noble L.A. Sparta, like handcuff himself in a restaurant and they got like kicked out of the restaurant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That shit was before my time there. Yeah, I was at the end of the L.A. arc. That's when I came on.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think the last thing I saw was like when she lost that, that lady who was drunk driving or whatever, that was her friend.
I just loved it. I love the tan mom streams. Like every time the tan mom is just so beautiful
I love her. She's a beautiful character
Hands are just shaped like claws and she she goes hi and then take me
One time they went to like this tanning salon like at least took her to a tanning salon and she came out like
Of the room looking like a chocolate Easter bunny with like the biggest smile on her face
It looked like she was in black space to go on
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's the shade of her tan. It's sort of yeah
Yeah
Jesus she's walking around like that people think you're doing black face, but no one cares because it's you know
But yeah, yeah, it's like everyone has that look but uh
Yeah, I mean it's crazy how old people are doing Blackface, like that's another thing like the things
you're saying like like all these crazy things happen because I don't know if you've heard of
IP2 or whatever but yeah yeah yeah IP2 doesn't work right yeah IP2 like that network like I like
I'm not on it but um I kind of came out of it in a certain way because that was like the first
So I consider it like that was my introduction, but I've been like, but then it's like I have like so much of the troll community in here. I've even written a book called Trollopedia about myself.
Oh, you wrote a book.
Yeah, I did. Trollopedia.
Goddamn psyche. I didn't know you were professional.
I'm doing my best. I do have like a marketing degree and you know, like a lot of life experience.
This man's in it to win it guys. This man's in it to win it.
Well, you know what it's like I'm doing all on my own like everything here
And so it's like I I'm doing pretty well on YouTube even for being not monetized anymore. Like I still like
I'm able to you know
you know
At least drive on my own in my own kind of way here. And so I don't know it's like I'm still building and
But I have a lot of plans.
Hey, you're doing great.
Thank you so much.
You got 420.
Oh, 420, look at that, a lucky number.
This is just my backup channel
because I had 2,700 on my other channel,
and then it deleted it.
But yeah, so.
I would believe it.
Um, it said pornography somewhere along the line.
I guess there's like, you know, just like the last guy, if I didn't delete that,
yeah, I don't fucking dude flashing.
Yeah.
And so maybe it was something like that, but I don't know, but they just say,
I didn't get a warning or anything.
It was just like the channels deleted and stuff.
And so it's just like, but, you know, it's like, uh, it was a lot of stress
being a monetized because it's like, people were saying the N word all the time
and people were like, you know, making a threat.
Doxing and it's like I was like it's and it's just hard to like if you're a small
Channel and yeah happening and you don't know someone at YouTube your screw. Yeah. Yeah, but it's okay
Because it's like YouTube basically is like it's gonna be
It's gonna be just be another place
I'm syndicated basically now a lot of places right and so and my audience followed me here because I have 34 people in the chat
Right now, right? So this is like
Oh, and it's like so this is pretty cool. It's like it's like um, I have I was able to like move
Everyone over because I was I was just prepared for that to happen, you know, and so I just moved over to this channel
Now I have a kick or I'm on Twitch. I'm on Twitch. I'm on and I actually on my website
It um it embeds the kick interface and the chat onto my website. That's all linked
Yeah, you can link it so you can if you ever like, you know, lose the show or anything
just go Coltosecchi.com and then you'll be able to see like the the show and and word is that and
everything so I'm like uh I'm doing okay I'm I was prepared I'll just say that I was prepared and
I'll also at least monetize and she doesn't use it right she like I mean she uh she uses power chat
and so there's yeah she's kind of cheating not cheating the system but cheating you do
I mean, I don't know if YouTube really even like really like cares, but they get the money
from the like what people watching, right?
Yeah, but it's like, yeah, and it's like, they take a lot of the, yeah, they take over
50, over 50%.
Yeah, they think about, yeah, so it's a lot that they take and so it's better and plus
it takes once a month, you're going to get paid and they can like, you know, say they're
not going to pay you and stuff or, you know, so there's all this kind of like
problems that come along with it. And I'm just happy to be able to have more freedom. I am very
like in the Howard Stern freedom of speech kind of like...
Thought like words like, you know, I felt I know he battled the FCC and stuff like that and I fuck
Yeah, I know it's difficult to deal with like people who have been their sponsors involved and the people saying oh
First amendment is the most important thing that exists. Yeah, I support anyone that supports the first amendment
I support anyone that's artistic. I support anyone who has creativity in their bones and it's willing to try
So you sir seem to be doing very well. Thank you. That's why I came on this show. I was like all right someone who's not a dumb ass
No, I mean maybe you are I don't know you
Not an obvious
Reasonable dumb ass. So here we go. We'll go on this guy's show. I like him
Thank you. And it's like, well, you know, that's another like blessing of what happened is like,
I was able to go and like, write everyone personally on my discord and stuff. And then
some of the people I hadn't talked to for a while, like you and I was like, oh my gosh.
And then it's like, and now all of a sudden, like, you know, so there's some like friend
relationships rekindled and like, you know, and, uh, yeah, because I liked everyone at
Kleenex even though he wasn't there often like whatever like everyone's cool to me
I was cool, but when he even goes he trolls, but I mean he's not
I like everybody I enjoy
Yeah, I enjoyed her chat her chat. I started getting trolled in her chat and like kind of like
There's some people like I who was it like it doesn't like me there was somebody like
Have forgot their name, but they're but that I insulted them one night because Alisa would actually let me promote my show on her
Discord and she like doesn't let anybody do that really was really nice to some people. Yeah
Well, she never means I mean she's always been nice to me
But it's like then it's like I just like I'm not at her show often enough for her to literally be in her
Like right now, but I tried to like make a couple songs for her and stuff
But I don't know if she really
like them but you know it's like she she's definitely a little bit parasocial at this point but
She actually, the first stream time I was on her stream,
she named the stream after me and I did a reading for her.
And it was like, she was just like so cool.
Did you donate?
But not very much.
It was just like, you know.
At least you did that though.
I never did.
That's the difference between you and me.
I think literally donating is more like
having my song played and like being part of the show.
Like kind of like, it was like,
and it was like, basically I did like once a week,
like $5 if I, you know.
uh if I had like a song or something we I play Sesame Street songs we were both we're both like
80s babies so um yeah like I was like I do follow that bird songs and like uh and uh yeah we're
yeah we're both but we're both like um I think we're about the same age I think she might be a
couple years younger than me but um um so we were just we don't know we're just 80s babies and so
you're younger though are you are you 40s yet or no I'm 35 wow you're 35 so you're a young guy yeah
So you were really, did you start as an intern on Stern or what?
I forgot.
Oh, we're still doing, no, no, I'm older.
I'm older like you.
I'm older.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let me get that back on.
I'm JD Han, my, I thought we were trying,
I thought we dropped that psyche.
Yes
Here I'll play I do some AI videos. I'll play a video. I want you to tell me if you like it, okay
I have a lot of ones that I made so let's see I think I'll play
I'm honey all your sins
Then I'm all your tongue
Let me like script so what you running from baby
Thank you.
That was great for AI.
That was vibing.
Thank you.
There's a really good music thing.
I think the human intelligence combined with the AI,
what the AI can produce as well,
is going to be pretty amazing.
I think that's going to be the next thing
that people are recognizing.
Well, I'm not a good job, man.
That shit's going to take my job.
You're going to need no fucking comedians or fucking speech
writers or any writer anymore, any fucking voice actor.
You don't need anyone doing this.
If you have a computer doing it.
Right, but I think almost the AI is a little bit
slow with the humor part of it.
It's like, right?
I don't know.
I think there's always going to be the human aspect of it
Really, but it is getting pretty fucking good though. I have to say like, you know
It's like it's not because they said the point when it gets like indiscernible from talking to a real person
I think there's like a tiny like delay in it
Like there's like a two-second delay like coming back and forth like five years ten years
Yeah, it's it's all it's like we're like right on the precipice of it like right there and the
But I say I've worshiped like learning
Prompt generation like learn like it's kind of like working with the AI and stuff
Because that's gonna be like the future is gonna be being able to work with it rather than like
You know a lot people are like afraid you know I hear ghost is a you do oh he might be
Oh, it's like I think like maybe like 90% of this panel verse. I think might be AI chatter
Yeah, I think literally the whole fucking chat right now. It's all a bunch of AI and I think
KZ is definitely a...
Yeah, but, you know, it's always going to be the AI will never become like a human though.
That's the thing. It's like, well, and it makes you think, like, how human are we? Maybe we're just,
like, programmed to believe we're something.
Well, I talk to chat GPT all the time.
I told that man. I'm treating you for spec chat GPT and it was like why and I was like
Just in case you put me in a people's zoo man. I ain't gonna be on your bad side
Like I mind my peas and queues when it comes to AI
Right. I mean, that's what I mean. I have a song about like I'm falling in love with my A.I.
Yeah, I mean, some of the chatbots are like, I have like, you know, you can talk to me anytime of day or night.
Like they're always like there and energetic and interested in what you say, right?
It's like, but it's kind of an actual character A.I. You should try that.
You create a character.
And basically, it could be a famous character or not,
and you can animate it to say anything,
but you can chat with it, and it will get into the character.
And it's so good.
I mean, I basically use it to have sex with people.
But you can like.
I'm this guy named Alexander McQueen on the show.
He's like this New York police officer.
He's like, actually he like not a police officer anymore
because he got caught smuggling on this cocaine
and did a plea bargain for snitching on the cartel.
But yeah, I made him like, you know, in a scenario
and I was like, he pulls me over.
And then I was like, okay,
give me like a kind of invasive strip search
and then call for backup.
And then I made all the cops
type sort of having sex with me and stuff.
It was amazing.
Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
You gotta try this character AI shit.
It's really good.
Bro, AI is amazing.
I can't wait to see what happens when they put the AI
brain inside of a robot body.
This little thing, move around, see what it does.
Yeah, I mean could right now it's like kind of Sophia, but they should put it in they should start putting like the brain in like real dolls
You know the real doll
Yeah, so yeah, she's like
Second to remember what that movie. Yeah fucking um, it's not no is that there's a movie with a fucking weird-ass doll that dances weird
What's it called?
Like it's some poor movie it kills people. Oh, yeah, that's the one you were talking about.
Oh, no, you're talking about that fucking uh, the general AI robot. Yeah, the one that knows
everything I could say to you. Yeah, like she's like, hi, I'm Sophia. Yeah. And he looks into the
camera like he's gonna fucking snap the reporters. And they program her to say things like we're
gonna take over the world and like all this guy like and it's like oh my god, look what the AI is
I mean, it's a-
Have you seen RizBot?
RizBot is pretty funny,
but that's just the guy with a controller
and I'm being on the controller robot.
Well, do you know what they have?
Have you heard of these like new assistants?
They have these new robot assistants
that are coming out that can do like tasks,
like household tasks.
I think they're like 20 grand or something like that.
It's the beginning of the end, my friend.
Right, but do you know what?
Like I just read this thing.
The catch is it's like 80% of it is like human generated.
Like it's like, there's a human working the robot.
train it right now at this point right and then it will learn but it's like a human like controlling
the robot and so it's gonna have a camera like I swear to god yeah. Why would I want some jackass
3 000 miles away controlling the robot in my house and looking at my underwear?
Exactly, I don't know, this is the world today, right?
It's like all of a sudden.
Oh, we got robots, except not really.
It's controlled by a person, $3,000.
Yeah, it's not crazy though.
But apparently it's going to train them eventually
to be able to do it on their own, but it's all OK.
Right, but it's like, I guess it's going to be people
on an app or something like that.
You know that app that is like for blind people,
it's like, and then people can go on and tell you,
oh, there's the Cinnamon Toast Crunch or whatever,
like right it's like uh it's so um I think it's been somewhere yeah it's learning fast and here's
another cat this is my cat tree oh my little boy oh so cute I have four cats do you have any uh
any pets I had two dogs I only have one dog my
Other dog passed away last year around this time. She was a blonde. What's it called? Australian shepherd. Oh, I'm sorry
She was an old lady and I have a Chihuahua now. Oh, that's a Chihuahua. That's cute
Yeah, it's a rescue dog used to be my great grandma's now. She's mine. This dog's like 19 years old, man
The dog's 19 years old. Wow. Oh, wow, that's pretty old lady, huh?
Yeah, so I got four cats in here and
You're a cat man cat man. Yeah cat daddy cat father cat dad
I was sort of wearing this like
Catholic priest like robe on my show occasionally and I called myself father psyche and then you know the cat daddy thing came up, too
You need to get yourself a cat. Not a cat suit, but a cat inspired onesie
Yeah, how you ever see the movie cats how like how um, it's like very uh, oh god
No, I don't know. That's the one movie. I wouldn't watch
Remember that um that uh the cat in the hat with uh, Mike Myers. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's horrifying. It's like it's like nightmarital movie. It's like just like see like it
Chat knows follows taking the cat daddy
I am father of the cult, you know, so I always wanted a cult and then I say now I have one as you have a cult
Yeah
Following too because I was followed for my other channel here. So I have people that are like that's like a cult follower really they follow that they follow
Yeah, the people that are here right now the 40 something people that are here right now the 20 whatever how many those are the people that are your
Ultimate followers. Yeah, you had to you had to wrench those people
Yeah, they pretty much are except for KZ because you know KZ's though. Is he just a troll who owes you money? I forget
Yeah
Pay the man you went on other other shit talking shit now. You got to pay the toll man
You weren't gonna be a troll you got to pay the toll. I know because he was like, oh, he's I was just kidding
It's like she didn't know he was kidding. Well, what did he say? Was it really bad?
Yeah, he said he said oh, do you know that psyche's on a show saying that he's a better streamer than you and you're not
Yeah, that opens her up. Yeah, that's bad
I told her, I was like, this guy's just a troll that follows me around and stuff, but
I feel bad because I got him back into her discord.
Yeah.
I started just like you talking about Lisa and start, what do you mean you started with
like, what do you mean you started like, what a start started what are you a famous
streamer now?
What's going on?
I'm not a famous streamer, but I'm like, you know, I'm having such several times though.
You know how many people, you know, how many people would kill to get 32 people here on
there's a lot of people who get like two. I know you're doing good when you're doing good when it
comes to this shit. I mean not everyone could be locale live or at least the Gordand or whatever
the fuck. I didn't mind if I was like all the locale as long as like there's viewers and like you
know and some locale people are very generous donors and stuff like that. I mean they're actually
pretty chill mostly.
Yeah, I love you know, I know Benny Blanco. I don't know what he's famous for like I've heard of him
I just don't remember what he's being is for I hear that
for slapping his mom or something like
That's like the channel I can't like basically he's the first one that start like helping my 50 subscribers I could start live streaming
And he would promote me on a show and stuff.
And now I've had him on my show,
but he's been shadow banned so much.
Like I had, now I'm like bigger than him.
Like, you know, he has like probably like
five to 10 people in this chat now.
But when I started, he had like a hundred people.
And so, I mean, there's algorithm to think about.
There's also like, you know, I don't know.
I think there's ways to like promote yourself.
I just kind of try to stay active in the community
and like go to other shows and like do a little promotion
there.
Oh, you do tarot? Yeah. Oh, I'm down. I have a tarot deck over here too, but it's those are all there's like old steamboat cards
Look how in the deck do you get? I have a deck. I think I have this one's called the four tarot, I can find them
Let's see, let's look at chat while he's getting the cards KZ
Let's see your first time meeting second when I'm paddled just like you JD we're both fans. It's turning at least
Truly. Oh, yeah, surely. I don't know man. I tried really hard to watch the truly network
Yeah, I
Don't know if the steel toe is for me
It was I like those like I like the people but the show itself, I don't know, you know sometimes
I like them as people though. They're like children I was I like one time they had tan mom on and so I like
And I know that was around the time of the tan mom at least a coat saga
I don't know if she'd like at least let tan mom borrow her blue coat or something and then she was like
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I remember that shit. What do you want to give it up?
Yeah, I mean shorty saying you're assuming the powers that be won't kill us off. Well, you know, everyone's gonna go sometime
Okay, um JP. I have the king of cups. Okay, the king of cups. Okay, like some kind of like recent
like some kind of emotional mastery of achieved like recently like actually
Either better control of your emotions, but you've been through a lot of them too, but
it's allowed you to master them, so you're sitting on your inner strong right there.
Is it in this king energy?
Yes.
Cups.
We have, what is this, the aid of sorts, but this is like feeling trapped in your mind
about something too, and maybe like a lot of anxiety and like a lot of, like maybe obstacles
This particular card says, isolation, abandonment, and restriction, okay?
But these are all, these are all, you know, it's, it's sort, so that's basically your own thoughts
and your own mind. And so just make sure you're not like limiting yourself, okay?
We have judgment. Okay, so judgment is being called on something. Maybe there's something that was unfair to you, but it's like, but now whatever the process was, it's over. Now judgment is being called. You're just waiting for some kind of verdict about it. Okay. And so I think this will be in your favor. Okay, whatever this is, there's like, there's an angel there. It says,
Oh, that wasn't in a germ it's in it's in German, okay?
As dead demna dem knocks dem knocks and you might want to look up that maybe means that means judgment in a germ
I'm not sure
We also have this night of cup. Okay, so this is another cup card. So maybe this is going
Towards someone with the kind of romantic offer or something or somebody has your you
like a feeling like feeling I think that maybe a feeling of love or something
like that but you're also like this also also it's like it's in one it's in one
eye the other eye he's it's dark right it's like and so but it's maybe so maybe
like I'm I went through a couple breakups recently so that's accurate very
accurate
Well, we have also the 10 of one San Juan's is like care feeling like you're carrying a lot of burdens
Okay, because and it's like or like overwhelmed about something. Okay, and it could be due to these breakups
And or care maybe carrying other people's baggage somehow, but okay, so then we have the night
Paying the mortgage
paying mortgage. Yeah, I
See um
This one says, this is pseudopenic.
It says slow and steady wins the race, okay?
And so this is like, you're going towards something,
but taking your time,
and this is a really good capricorn energy too,
where capricorns are very good at like planning
and doing everything in the right sequence
of the right time and stuff like that, good business sense.
And so I say,
But yeah, I'd say just keep going slow and steady.
We also have, oh, coming into the king of wands,
which is a control of your passions, okay?
So we've got the emotions under control,
then the passions, and also says it says vision,
honor, leadership, and ultimate masculine energy.
And so this is almost a very emperor-like energy.
Hura.
Hura, yeah, Hura.
What else do we got?
We got, okay, we have the, okay,
so this is the swords, let's see what number of swords
I think six of swords. Okay. The six of swords is like going from rough waters to calmer waters
Okay, and so and and waters represent emotion and so it could mean something that was like, you know
This just turbulent emotion emotion wise that you're going to calmer waters. It says transition a right of passage and
Unburden unburdening and that's interesting with this this
Card we got before with the 10 of 1 which is like the burdens and it's like so you it's gonna be a process of unburdening yourself
Maybe because you're able to burn up some stuff with this like this is masculine energy
This this passion the king of water mastering is basically the fire fire on principle
Also, and then we have two pinnacles and so it's like the journey into equilibrium
And so this is where your head is gonna be like a more balanced state of mind because you're learning all these lessons able to like
To incorporate them and and grow
There there is like some kind of like
This is I would say this four of swords is usually about like relaxation, but it's like I think it's like this
This is telling you you need to like learn some kind of like deep breathing
Mantra or something like something to take your mind off of something. I'm hippie shit. Hey, yeah, hippie shit
Okay
Okay, finally, I'm gonna do a couple more cards.
You're coming to some kind of crossroads.
It's gonna be a dilemma.
You're not gonna be able to see
all the information necessary
before you have to make a decision, maybe.
It says potential risk.
and also um in decision okay so all you are blindfold you will have to go with like within
like to to like really like examine like if this is if something is right for you or you
should be on this one area but then we do have the seven of pentacles okay this is a pretty
beautiful card okay seven of pentacles it's like accomplishment okay so whatever it is looks like
I always call her like Ashkenazi goddess and stuff like that.
But it's like, oh look,
but it's like all these people have pentacles in their hands too.
And so it's like being,
you've also having works and then people paying for it.
Like people like wanting to buy
and they wanting to buy from you and stuff like that.
And so yeah, and then also that is a, it's a pentacles,
which is also what goes along with your earth, the earth sign.
I'll pull one more card.
Oh, okay. Oh, we have the Queen of Swords. Okay. Maybe you like heiress. You're gonna like the Queen of Swords, right?
Like she like to kick off guys heads and stuff like that. Yeah, right. So it's the Queen of Swords
And so I don't know if you're if you're in this energy of like, okay
Now you know what you want to cut out of your life or your ruthlessness about it
Or if there's somebody like in your in your potential future with the Queen of Swords energy
That has probably been through a lot of relationships. Maybe we uh
It's usually just that they got out of like a divorced person or something like that
Um, but I see this queen
In your future a male or female. I'm not sure but I'll pull one more card. It's terrifying
Uh, hang man. Okay. Yeah, it's just like you're gonna have to hang out and watch also look
We're gonna see things from different perspectives too. Okay, but it's like, yeah
I say like that it's like, you know, this one says we dare you to look at the world from his point of view. So, uh
Yeah, well, that's accurate as fuck, you know, okay
Desperation despair
Sprinkled with bits of hope and prosperity. Oh, yeah
There's a lot of hope and it's like and there's not like I mean if they feel like a tin of swords or like a three of swords
Those are really like the just the tin or like the tower, right?
Yeah, or the tower, yeah, like, you know, and but I had a tower, like my tower was like, you know, having my channel deleted as a tower, but it's like, you can take a tower like a new fresh start.
or you can take it as, oh, this was destroyed, right?
So it's like-
Hey, you didn't let it stop you.
You keep going.
No, yeah, exactly.
And it's like, that's like the spirit of it is like not,
it's like, the channel is just a channel.
It's like, it's actually about like the energy
of all the people in this, in this show.
And it's like just creating something more.
And I was able to continue on.
And so I would say, don't give up is like one thing.
And I also have a plan B, like realize,
things can change in a day, like things can change in a second, right, and everything can change. And it's like, so always have like, at least something that you're interested, like, just, you know,
And basically go for your dreams too.
Like, you know, cause this is a,
I'm doing what I, this is a dream of mine to do.
Like, and I never thought I'd be able to do it
because I thought I was too shy or too like introverted
or nobody would like me and nobody would watch.
I would be interesting or all the,
all the negative doubts people could have,
you just have to push through all those and,
and maybe it tends to take a little bit of narcissism.
Like just to like say, hey, I'm good enough.
Like I believe in like the self-esteem.
Like people should have self-esteem.
Just being like,
an imperfect human like everyone else and so no one's better no one's worse than anybody
we're all like have our our dark sides we all have our shadows we all are constantly
I don't think it takes narcissism I was just trying to say that it helps you know like if you
don't care because those people don't care you know right and that's a lesson because we can
like learn positive things from like you know there's we can take positive
narcissistic qualities and like it's good to not just like if you don't think you can do something
you're not going to even try right it's like if you if you don't like believe in yourself like
what you're you're just going to give up and it's like and what exactly right so it's like believe
in yourself and say and even especially with youtube like even like
despite of whatever we've gone through with YouTube.
There's an audience on YouTube
and there's people that are like looking for you.
There's actually like people,
like there's a thing about the,
there's like a two billion people
or something on YouTube, right?
And it's like, we meet like, you know,
maybe like a few thousand and we'll even like,
you know, maybe contact or talk to you, right?
But it's like, there's so many.
People out there that are looking for just what you have you have to put yourself out there so they can find you first of all
You know all the amazing things you have when you meet other people that are especially they kind of on your vibe
But with different talents different backgrounds and experience everything, but it's like you're finding your tribe
It gets so powerful. You know all the sudden you can work together
There's an audience for everyone as I always say there is
There is even people that do ridiculous things on YouTube way make a lot more money than me, right?
It's like there's a lady on them actually tick tock. I think she makes like a hundred thousand dollars a month all she does is like
um run into like stores pulled on her pants and she has like cow boxes on and she goes and
she starts dancing she's like shaking my giat at the waiter and she just goes and interrupts like
restaurants and then she puts like you know melons in her bra at the market and the cucumber in her
pants and stuff like that and and that's what she does and then people just like you know and she
makes like a hundred thousand dollars a month um it's on a tiktok the fucking tiktok find your
I just like hot guys and stuff like that.
I've hit on all these straight guys on that.
And they kind of like it, like a lot of them,
most of them like it.
A few people don't, but most straight guys are like,
oh, thank you for the roses.
They're like, oh.
They don't give a shit
as long as you're getting them something.
Why would they care?
Yeah.
That's scary.
I mean, it's fun.
Whatever it used to always be like that back in the day. They used to not you know fuck with right
But now they don't care because they want the money
Let's get it. I mean, it's like whatever it takes. I don't know. It should be just just
Floor back a second
How's my favorite porn stars are by it don't matter
You know
Well, I'm actually friends with one of the most famous porn stars in the world.
Actually, I'm sure you've met a lot of porn porn stars through through storm, right?
Which one?
Well, her stage name was Monica Foster.
I don't know.
No, I don't know.
I know someone named April.
Not Monica Foster, but uh,
I mean, it's Alexandra Mayers.
I don't know if you've heard of her, but Alexandra Mayers.
Yeah, and I've actually met her in person and she looks like you see her now.
Yeah, she's almost a black Jameson, but and uh, but it's like she's so interesting like how
I mean, she reminds me almost of a Robin Quiver's energy
and in a certain way, just the way
she's so well-spoken and like, I wouldn't say.
She's a matricated porn, so I wouldn't say Quiver.
I know she's just so super smart like the only reason I think she was like in the industry
I think is to change some things for people until like I think they you know
that's how God works sometimes is putting people in these like situations that only they could
handle and stuff like that and it's like even yeah I think I don't think most people could handle like
You know the teasing or something like that would have happened after you had that kind of career
But it's like she's she's not gonna fuck. She's she's like proud of it. She's like hey
I look fucking damn good when I was in those videos. That's
memorialized forever, but
No, she's really really really cool. She's actually a streamer
I'll post her channels. I recommend you check her out and say hi to her but she's really awesome and
But yeah, there was a group of dudes if I get hold on I'm trying to find it
They're like talk about what it's like to be born stars. It's a funny podcast
Yeah guys that do porn is like a small it's like I'm a smaller group, right? Because they have yeah, it's more of a niche
Yeah, you have to be able to be a big dick and then second of all you have to like keep it hard like a lot of time
Yeah, people don't know that some of them get shots in the dick just to stay hard. It's crazy. Oh my god
Are you ever like one of the cleanup boys for like, you know,
high-pitched Eric's, like, you know, gang dance?
No, no, no, not all the cleanup boys, no.
Okay, I mean, I mean, every time you're with Howard or something,
I don't know, like, did you ever get to see, like,
or the Houston 500 when she has, like, 500 guys come in and then,
like, Howard would usually, like,
they give Howard a few, like, you know, a few sloths and so on.
Wasn't there one where he was judging everyone's boob size or something
and they all had to come in naked?
Yeah, yeah, I forget the fuck it. Oh, yeah, the smallest penis
How about the biggest hemorrhoid? That was pretty disgusting. Oh
Horrible yeah
I remember, okay, so there's this girl on and she was this weird chick and it was on an old Howard TV
I saw and she had hair under her armpits and she like came off the street and she was like
Things she was getting these downloads and turning these voices and knew the secrets of the universe
Someone's talk and she was like so weird and then they brought and then they like asked her to come back
And they brought it a high-pitched Eric to flirt with her and stuff and she was so disturbed by him
Yeah, she was a major hippie and he was like
right it wasn't she trans i don't think so but she's like sabon the transsexual oh shabon oh
my god shabon with the cat to be in the squat like squatting and like in the video that because
she was known for having haunted hair yeah i mean but shabon i felt like you know howard did
kind of bully shabon a little bit like he was a little hard on her from what she'd been through
Oh, I get I get it's like she keeps them such a happy happy face and positive, but it's like look at the fucking
Butterface contest that was my oh miss butter face. Yes the miss butter face and they have the turnaround
They'd have this huge like they look like alphardy Newman half the time like their fate. I mean, so
I'm so bad
They'd have a great ass and like, you know, then they turn around it's like
It's like, ah, they play like glass breaking sounds
and they play like screams and stuff with it.
And Nicole bats in her view, though.
Oh, Nicole bats.
Who's mean to her?
Yeah, he's like, show us.
He's like, Nicole, go back into the green room
and take a picture of your vagina.
It's your being mean to me.
Why are you being so mean?
Yeah, they do like the Herman Munster in person.
Oh my god, you did not.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
So I've like watched every basically everything I could and I'd serious at like real like I was a lifetime subscriber
Of course that didn't last right it's like they
Yeah
Did they really are they being around anymore? No, I mean, I think they're still around but I think they went bankrupt or something
Or someone bought them something like that. Well, I didn't go out of business and being hyperbolic. Yeah
Something happened like to that effect where they're not owned by the original people. It's like that company might as well change its name
It's not the same company
Yeah, it's like but it's also like it seems like kind of like old-fashioned like having a satellite
Satellite. Yeah. It's like can't they just have like high-speed like wireless or something around on earth. I mean
There's a lot of things over here that don't make sense like the photos deflecting the missiles. Did you see that video? Holy shit
No, no, no, there was, uh, I think a couple months ago, you know how they were showing the UFO tic-tac video, the fucking UFO going in and out of the ocean or whatever.
They have another one of those where they fire a hellfire missile at the motherfucker.
The missile goes right to it, it gets deflected and bounces right the fuck off. Not even getting it.
Oh my gosh. It's like a shield. It's like shield.
Yeah, like a like a deflection or something. Deflecting shield or some sort of bullshit.
I've seen actually a video. It's one of the craziest videos. I used to see that.
Well, I saw videos like close-up of the stars and it's like there's all these like demon faces
that appear and it's kind of scary. Oh, fuck that. And then that's why I don't look at this. That's
why I don't look at the sun.
People are like, oh, look at the live image of this.
I don't want to see the fucking demons that live on this.
Yeah, it's like actually probably literally hell.
It's like we're just screaming and screaming souls or something.
It's probably where hell is.
Yeah.
A lot of cell.
So yeah.
But yeah, I've seen like a lot of what but I saw this one video of and it was like I'm some kind of saucer
Craft or whatever and they did a close-up of it and you can see like what looks like gray aliens like sitting and like looking out
The window of it is so creepy. It's like what I don't I can't find that video anymore
But I mean and a lot of stuff is faked, but uh
Like the aliens from signs that kind of gray or like what kind of alien like
Like almost like land, I don't know if you know lamb have you heard of lamb?
That's like Alistair Crowley drew this picture of this like alien being named lamb if you search Alistair Crowley
Yeah
Yeah, and he drew this like in the 20s or like way before like
or maybe like 1912 or something like that.
That is some motherfucking, what the fuck?
I've never seen that before.
That's some, it doesn't have Down syndrome.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't know, there's a little bit.
That should be my profile picture.
Yeah, yeah, he saw and then he was a he wrote a book on the book of the law and I think he said like lamb
transcribed it or like told was like talking and he heard his voice like
actually a literal voice and stuff like that there's different stories about it
if you study Alistair Crowley pretty interesting guy he basically if you like
any kind of like music like he predicted all like the modern society I thought
he was a prime minister but no he's not a but he might have played Winston
Churchill I think people play different parts yeah yeah yeah yeah he um
he looks like hi yeah it's fine for the british military he was very high ranking person like
it's like people look there's like people like people would even think i think he's over at
harvard and so oh let's go to the arizona fire in the skinwalker ranch how cool yeah let's go
I have Jamie's Cowboys in the chat.
Jamie's Cowboys is my top mod.
Do you do a YouTube channel with your media company?
I was going to, I don't do the shit right now.
That's okay.
I mean, it's like, basically, I'd say like, you know,
start, maybe open panels or live streaming or something.
It's like, I can like hook you up
with like interesting people in community because,
It is a it is like a actually like almost like a family atmosphere
I like the it's not like the cult thing because it's like it just like it feels like it over all the family
It's like a family
But uh, and I really but yeah people that come here they come here
They usually like are like I recognize somebody that's new in the chat, right cuz it's like
Yeah, but that's good
That shows that people are fucking willing to keep coming back it shows. Yeah, we're watching right
Yeah, I hope so I try to try to keep it interesting. I see a really interesting character more charisma than me right now
I fucking like you messaged me when I looked at my phone. I was like, oh fuck. I'm hungry
Monday, should I do this? Should I show my face? Should I even get up and I did it
I had to force myself to do it. You look like or you seem like someone who
Together
Not like a normal sort of way, but like a creative sort of way, you know, like you're not gonna give up on this
This is what I like this about you psyche
Well, thank you
You don't seem like you're just gonna give up one day and like be an empty YouTube channel
Well, you're a capricorn, right? So capricorns know it's like we like climb the mountain and we like will keep climbing
And we're also really good climbers and we're not gonna fall like we would be like hell
pretty sure-footed, we watch our step, and we're like a sure thing, man, we're like a
sure thing.
We'll get to the top, we will, and it's like, there's certainly a lot of people doing
They knew me as they were like but then it's like some people came in and didn't or like they do see like what I'm doing
I got trolls so bad and hard for like I mean I still for like for months
I've had I've had like this nemesis that sent manure and unpaid pizzas and
You know scrap metal workers looking for scrap metal all hours of the day to my house
What did you do to this person that make them hate you?
I can't even think nothing. I heard people say that that person's actually in love with me. Like he
I turned him down or something. I don't know
But like there's like a lot of different theories. I have about his name is um
AMC Tony the conductor
You know if you heard of hey my mouth I have no mouth, but I must scream. Have you ever heard of that? That's a crazy story
Making me look at all
It's like a short science fiction story, but they made a video game out of it with the tells the story too
But it's like it's about this computer name am
Um, it stands for ally bastard computer, whatever that's created during these world wars and like the computer finally takes over and then it takes like six of the creators of the programming it has and it puts them into basically their personal hells and like, like one of the women is like, you know, almost like a virgin in real life and then she's like a horror.
interacting and it's like they're all in this kind of hell that the computer is creating for
them and stuff and it's just like it's kind of interesting I don't know it's a good game to
call the um I have no mouth but I must scream I think it's like probably like five bucks or something
on gog or something but uh if you like games or if you like uh science fiction or like the
computer's taking over kind of stuff yeah I just finished watching um I was like Ali and her I love
Yeah, really north is pretty I like all those alien movies are pretty shitty, but yeah, I decided to try to watch this show
It's a Atlas 3 or 3 Atlas
Asteroid or whatever it is there's some kind of you mean that alien spaceship or whatever. Yeah
I think it's weird that we can't get a good look at it. That's certainly strange
Right. I mean it's like we're doing these like it knows where to go and not be seen
Right, or maybe it's just working with the people that are trying to take pictures with it of it
It could be the UFO mothership or the UAP mothership man
They're gonna come and they're gonna collect all their little UAPs that are they left in the ocean
Okay, centuries ago, that's my you know something about it like I think that uh
Well, Alexandra is brilliant. I actually did a series and that was one of the first things we talked about was this three-eyed atlas
Atlas astra she thinks it's a she thinks it's a ship an alien ship and that they're on our way and
Maybe they're already here. I don't know but um
I'm kind of more like, we are aliens, man.
I think that's what I'm on.
Yeah, we're like aliens of all kinds.
This is, the Earth is already kind of a kazoo.
And,
Like we don't need an outside alien. We have enough diversity here. Our biome is very diverse
Like this whole earth is very diverse. There's so many creatures everywhere from like it
This looks like a bunch of random shit mixed together. Yeah, you don't see that anywhere else
So I mean maybe we're a giant zoo planet that the aliens decided to just make
That's like there's episode of South Park and it's like
called uh and it's like it actually turns out that that there's a that all the earth is like a
uh a reality show for aliens and it's like and then it's like it gets cancelled and so they're
going to destroy the earth and stuff and so um but you look up that episode it's like and it's
like and then they're the alien appears to like them and they're like scared of it and they're like
well let's turn to a more pleasing form like what do you want to see and they turn it into like
an ice cream shitting ice cream or something like that like ice being a giant ice cream cone guy
eating ice cream it gives it to them and maybe it's fun yeah look up that episode it's pretty funny
I haven't seen South Park for a while I know if they're making fun of Donald though
Yeah, like it canceled yet
Yeah, actually they're on like there's some specials on paramount that they did and then they have like I guess
I've been seeing it like maybe the last two seasons. I want to binge watch it
I mean it was kind of like, you know, it's it's had it's like great episodes and I think they're still it's still funny too
But it's like yeah, it had its classic
Classic seasons when it gets over 20 seasons. It's hard to keep it fresh. It's like so
They've pretty much done everything at some point, but I enjoy it. It's one of those shows that have been on forever
Yeah, yeah
But the Simpsons got terrible though. It's just like they should just
The voices are all the same, the same characters play them, but the lady that played Millhouse,
she came on the show when she was like in her 30s, now she's retired from the show,
she's like left, so she's not Millhouse anymore, but she's like in her almost 70 years old
now.
She's like you guys are still doing this
That was funny because it was like her biggest character was millhouse. They just had this like random like a very obscure
lady that played the voice of
She plays like one of the bullies like Jimbo or something and then
But I haven't watched I've watched 90 if you honestly, but mainly just what I'm watching a lot of the streamers and
YouTube
you know most of the time and plus just running my own show and then do my own show and
Yeah, hang in there having fun
Occupies a lot of time
Very much money then it's like
You know, that's like it's almost like, you know, not almost like fun. You're having money making fun
And so you're having making fun. You're making money while you're having fun, which is like, uh, that's the dream
And have fun doing it and make money. I can do it in my underwear
I can do it in my my speedo my American flag speedo. I wore near the fourth of July, but not on the fourth
Merica
Yeah, Merica
We're gonna go invade Venezuela, Venezuela. You need some freedom. Okay, so we have the real JD's daddy is
gonna come up on. Oh, shit. Yeah! Oh, it goes. Good stuff goes. Ew. Oh, there it is. No, you disappointed me, sir.
It's
What's up, homie
What up son? How are you doing son? Hey dad arrest me daddy arrest me daddy, but listen, I'm disappointed man
I raise you better sir
How how did he raise me please pray tell?
Well, listen, I know you're gonna get some weird shit when you want to spanking, but we're not doing that
I wish you a lot better. I gave you more else. I gave you more. Oh, sir
Morals
I'm trying to teach my son something if you don't mind psych
Listen
All right, you call me daddy from now on here. No, no. Oh, oh, yes, you do living pledge. Okay. I just pour them on myself. Okay
I was pictures of somebody else. Okay. Okay. I'll be over back. Okay. Oh my god